<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Green Wave Consulting]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Green Wave Consulting]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/wav/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:20:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/wav/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WAV]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WAV</h1><p>Green Wave is a premier professional services and business consulting firm. As trusted advisors to our clients, Green Wave provides a full array of integrated services, to clients across industry spectrum and in all stages of organizational development.   The collaborative culture at Green Wave enables our firm to continually review and enhance best practices and technological capabilities. The experience and insight gained through industry wide cooperation also allows our professionals to learn with industry leaders and innovators. As a result, our dedicated advisory professionals are experts in their fields, harmonizing with clients to anticipate opportunities on the horizon rather than react to short-term competitive pressures.   Consistent and consequential communication with our clients has been a hallmark of our firm since its inception. Green Wave regularly produces analyses highlighting emerging trends that will shape best practices.   At the core of Green Wave we possess an entrepreneurial spirit that mirrors that of the sophisticated business and financial services communities that we serve.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wav/wav/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee5e7412-20f4-4ab1-821c-9d3df2049bf6</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:37:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Know What MVP Is? You Need To]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Know What MVP Is? You Need To</h1><p>If you spend little time in the business and startup world, you may be excused for thinking MVP stands for most valuable player. But those three letters have a different meaning when it comes to innovation, business creation, and product launch. In this universe, MVP means minimally viable product.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6e818b68c049049dd81f8dba32477a5c09f01ca8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.inc.com/adam-fridman/5-reasons-why-utilizing-mvp-is-everything.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7dfaade6-0834-4977-8505-c985671ffc78</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:19:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Create a Positioning Statement That Stands Out]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How to Create a Positioning Statement That Stands Out</h1><p>In The Marketing Plan Handbook , author Robert W. Bly explains how you can develop big-picture marketing plans for pennies on the dollar with his 12-step marketing plan. In this edited excerpt, Bly offer an easy formula for crafting a positioning statement that will help you reach your prospects with the right marketing messages.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4650a6d460c644ecb997b445d5f1adbfeeb75125.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://entm.ag/1QcIy7l</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">20a7131b-60d9-4b0a-a5cb-a7608d71ee50</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Sales Skills to Make Your Business Thrive]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>5 Sales Skills to Make Your Business Thrive</h1><p>In Real Leaders Don't Follow , author Steve Tobak explains how real entrepreneurs can start, build, and run successful companies in highly competitive global markets. He provides unique insights from an insider perspective to help you make better-informed business and leadership decisions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a1b4429c9f13b3e4c451e91501c405f29f78e589.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/250854</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">052abfa2-f6a8-49f9-a02f-ceba12150f86</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["The Extra Mile Is Never Crowded"]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>"The Extra Mile Is Never Crowded"</h1><p>Every day, when you get to work or start your projects, you get to decide how much effort you're going to put in. A little, the normal amount, or go completely overboard. Few choose that last option, which gives you an advantage.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f6e439f5f48cc52b2f5e0d1fb8a27b694c5f94c8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://lifehac.kr/RPmQgti</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eeb73efc-adaa-4803-812c-ed86880c8ba5</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>957 Discovery Circle NE Unit#103 Issaquah, WA 98029 </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.grnwav.co/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1f08a651-1a37-4463-9a97-0f18dcce1438</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FI.co: Show, Don't Tell Your Startup Pitch To Investors]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>FI.co: Show, Don't Tell Your Startup Pitch To Investors</h1><p>In our previous webinar, How To Create A Great Elevator Pitch, Carter Laren and Adeo Ressi discussed the struggles that many founders face when pitching to investors, customers, employees and other...</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ed81a0864c5b5c92fb9f0fb4d15d849837095905.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fi.co/posts/20851</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5eba7711-5ccf-4d54-acbc-e885dd600455</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Plans: A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Business Plans: A Step-by-Step Guide</h1><p>A business plan is a written description of your business's future, a document that tells what you plan to do and how you plan to do it. If you jot down a paragraph on the back of an envelope describing your business strategy, you've written a plan, or at least the germ of a plan.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3a5e3ccc7c131c9b2fa3b90f4b3ba031e1fea063.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://entm.ag/1NQAV1N</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4f5f7978-df1e-4cce-8ca8-2a058a133655</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 20:14:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 Brutally Honest Success Lessons from Kevin O'Leary of Shark Tank]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10 Brutally Honest Success Lessons from Kevin O'Leary of Shark Tank</h1><p>Kevin O'Leary is a Canadian born entrepreneur and TV personality who rose to prominence in the business world after his software company sold to Mattel for $3.65 Billion in 1999. He is best known for his no-nonsense and often blunt criticism of aspiring entrepreneurs and startups on ABC's Shark Tank.</p><img src="http://addicted2success.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/Kevin-OLeary.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://addicted2success.com/success-advice/10-brutally-honest-success-lessons-from-kevin-oleary-of-shark-tank/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01f46080-3a48-4ad6-ae58-54af7377a77c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 20:14:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>