<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Green Wave Consulting]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Green Wave Consulting]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/wav/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 15:32:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/wav/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insight]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Insight</h1><p>Green Wave is here to help you and your company.  We team with industry leaders to create an array of unique strategies to ensure the fruition of your business.   In today's ever changing environments it is essential to stay at the top of the pack, often times this means a restructuring of current practices.  Green Wave has advanced practice of LEAN evaluation, creation,and integration of emerging practices and specialize in customized integration into your current practices to make the most profitable and least invasive structuring available.   Start-up and structuring of a new venture is a very difficult and time consuming part of any business.  We have developed state of the art ways to create and package your company to ensure the greatest availability to funding potential.  Thus allowing you to concentrate on the progression of ideas and concepts.   Personnel management is often times a tough yet integral part of any business, with advancement of human resource development we can ensure smooth transitions for acquisition and termination practices thereby reducing unnecessary resistance in daily operations.   Vetted advanced corporate LEAN processes including JIT, efficiency expertise, and flow management.  We take the latest advancements in the Technology industry and seamlessly integrate them into your existing structure.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wav/insight/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e2fb53-ce87-4a63-87c5-f732aee209ee</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 15:32:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[50 Steps Every Entrepreneur Must Take to Build a Business]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>50 Steps Every Entrepreneur Must Take to Build a Business</h1><p>Starting a business is one of the most challenging and rewarding things you'll ever do. The process is simpler than you might imagine, but to try to boil it down to five or 10 steps is an underestimation and an injustice.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c54eba22c6a5bab039ef2a0baff8e50308fe110e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/252811</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eb6e6d01-d4e1-4296-bf09-5eb9c3ce47f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 23:11:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[These 8 Disciplines Define a Fundable Entrepreneur]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>These 8 Disciplines Define a Fundable Entrepreneur</h1><p>Aspiring entrepreneurs often ask me what to do first when starting a business. Let me assure you, there is no absolute right or wrong, but there is real value in doing things in a sequence that minimizes the risks, optimizes your efforts and generates the best "first impression" on potential investors.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b4e71506954d95528e7d4d29f749b3d827123ce2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/252980</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c82b495f-ff78-4898-8787-1116c8629598</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:20:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Know What MVP Is? You Need To]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Know What MVP Is? You Need To</h1><p>If you spend little time in the business and startup world, you may be excused for thinking MVP stands for most valuable player. But those three letters have a different meaning when it comes to innovation, business creation, and product launch. In this universe, MVP means minimally viable product.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/be3984d0dd2aa79a9d9b2c453a75cd05abd5751f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.inc.com/adam-fridman/5-reasons-why-utilizing-mvp-is-everything.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7dfaade6-0834-4977-8505-c985671ffc78</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:19:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Create a Positioning Statement That Stands Out]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How to Create a Positioning Statement That Stands Out</h1><p>In The Marketing Plan Handbook , author Robert W. Bly explains how you can develop big-picture marketing plans for pennies on the dollar with his 12-step marketing plan. In this edited excerpt, Bly offer an easy formula for crafting a positioning statement that will help you reach your prospects with the right marketing messages.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4650a6d460c644ecb997b445d5f1adbfeeb75125.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://entm.ag/1QcIy7l</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">20a7131b-60d9-4b0a-a5cb-a7608d71ee50</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 17:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>